回忆过往，生命的必经之途；
Remembrance, part of every life;
无数悔恨，时间如河水流淌。
num'rous regrets, the art of passing time.
终生难忘，焚膏继晷的每夜；
Not one forgets, spent nights of chasing days;
两眼阖上，所见已灰飞烟灭。
eternal rest, to witness being erased.
所见已灰飞烟灭。
To witness being erased.
绝非寻常，以现今来讲；
It is seldom seen in this world of now;
备受景仰，世间都一样。
it is welcome, universe and out.
没有陪伴，汝得只身行；
It is seen, only from eyes of thine;
没有代价？一切尽是命。
is it free? 'Tis only by invite.
回忆过往，生命的必经之途；
Remembrance, part of every life;
无数悔恨，时间如河水流淌。
num'rous regrets, the art of passing time.
终生难忘，焚膏继晷的每夜；
Not one forgets, spent nights of chasing days;
两眼阖上，所见已灰飞烟灭。
eternal rest, to witness being erased.
所见已灰飞烟灭。
To witness being erased.
如此沉重，迫切想看透未来，
It is ponderous, willing to know my fate,
如此漫长，早已等得不耐烦。
in its longest lingering while to wait.
我能看到，记忆被翻来覆去，
I can see, memory taken tolls,
我还需要，时间来接受离去。
I'm not ready, not ready to let them go.
回忆过往，生命的必经之途；
Remembrance, part of every life;
无数悔恨，时间如河水流淌。
num'rous regrets, the art of passing time.
终生难忘，焚膏继晷的每夜；
Not one forgets, spent nights of chasing days;
两眼阖上，所见已灰飞烟灭。
eternal rest, to witness being erased.
所见已灰飞烟灭。
To witness being erased.